

# Hamza Guermaj

# CONTACT

- Ahl Loughlam, Rue 25, Sidi Moumen. Casablanca
- 0646-124435
- guermaj.h@icloud.com

**.....** 06-12-1994

### **SKILLS**

- Microsoft office365 suite
- Python / C
- MAC/Windows troubleshoot
- PLC Tia portal / SCADA
- Teamwork and versatility
- Stress resistance and autonomy
- Taking initiative and curiosity to learn.

### LANGUAGES

English: Fluent French: Good

**Arabic: Mother tongue** 

#### **PROFILE**

Coming from a technical background, having gone through a diversified path of experiences focused by my passion for the technical field and to find solutions using my technical assets, while bringing real added value to my workplace.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

## **English-speaking Technical Support Agent -AnyTech365**

Casablanca | Mars. 2021 - April 2023

Providing solutions to problems related to IT and computer networks.

### Franco-English-speaking Technical Support -GEMCAR

Casablanca | Dec. 2019 – Jan. 2021

Technical support for automotive software for a Canadian customer base.

### After-sales Service Technician - MEDITECH

Meknes | Nov. 2018- Feb. 2019

Ensure the after-sales service of biomedical equipment

halana in Automotion and Industrial Commutina

#### **Maintenance Technician - RADIOLOMED**

Casablanca | April. 2016 - Feb. 2018

Curative and preventive maintenance for biomedical equipment.

### **FORMATION**

Lycée Technique Mly. Abdallah

Hassan II Settat University	Casablanca
BTS Electronic Systems Ibn Sina Tech High School	2013-2015 Kenitra
BAC of Electrical Science and Technology	2012

2010 2010

Sidi Kacem